Fu Binyan,
you're finally back.
Actually, I have something
I want to tell you.
Wait a minute.
We also have something to tell you.
Come, sit.
Fu Binyan,
we all know
about your heart disease.
Chi Jia has prepared these for you:
Suxiao Jiuxin Wan,
nitroglycerin,
and...
It's all here.
Take whatever you need.
And this:
we bought you
a thermos.
If you need hot water,
just ask us.
We also applied to the school
for an AED.
We hope we won't need it,
but it's better to be safe than sorry.
Do you want me to do this too?
We'll try our best to take care of you.
So,
you can't slack off on your work either.
And you are our
data analyst.
The big game is coming up.
You need to give it your all.
Exactly.
Coach Su and I
can discuss tactics,
but no one can replace
your data analysis and advice.
And
did you secretly
give Lin Qingyuan extra training?
That's not fair!
I heard the center of Fanghe No.3 Middle School
is really good.
You have to analyze it for me.
You've finished?
It's my turn.
Or you can stop talking.
I don't dare to hear it.
Actually, what I want to say
is to let you
keep me here
to continue my work.
Great!
I knew you would
stay in the Basketball Club.
What's wrong? What's wrong?
Oh my god.
Medicine.
This is effective.
Quickly.
I scared you.
You always make this kind of joke.
Please.
Don't make
such a hellish joke, okay?
My heart can't stand it.
You scared me to death.
All right.
Let's start training.
If anyone doesn't listen to me,
I'm afraid that
my heart will have a problem.
Okay.
Let's go.
I'm leaving.
Wait.
Li Haoyu.
Fu Binyan.
You're finally back.
This is the latest smartwatch
I bought for you.
It's connected to
our phones.
It can monitor
your heart rate in real time.
We'll notice if anything goes wrong
and help you.
So,
please don't leave us again.
That's good.
Yeah.
Good.
Thank you.
Then let's
continue to train.
Go.
Come on.
Our goal
is not to pretend that this is not the case,
and keep him in the Basketball Club.
But to let him know that
although he has this disease,
he can still
be his original self.
We will also continue to accompany him
to be the original Fu Binyan.
Just like
Yu Hua played football with Shi Tiesheng.
I've already thought of a way.
We just tell him...
By the way,
you guys are too mean.
How come in the end,
I don't know you have heart disease?
I didn't want to tell anyone.
but it was accidentally
discovered by someone else.
I can testify.
He didn't even tell me at first.
Then why don't you accidentally
discover it from me?
Is it possible
that you are too careless
to find it out?
Don't say that.
I'm about to become
a mature and composed adult.
You have to trust me in the future.
What are you going to act out this time?
I have very important news
to tell you.
What?
I'm going to have siblings.
Siblings?
Food and drink are all ready.
You can start now.
Well,
do you have to
come to the secret base to hear me talk?
None of us have siblings.
We're curious.
Why isn't Xu Anbo
here at this time?
He has the most say.
He went back to take photos for Chi Jia.
He is really a good brother.
Xu Anbo
was born only three minutes earlier than his sister,
while I
am fifteen years older than my younger brothers and sisters.
An elder brother is like a father.
I have to be reliable.
So, these days,
your parents must be very busy, right?
Yes.
They took a year's leave together.
You're due soon, right?
No,
they're thinking
of taking a half-month break now
and heading out next week.
Road trip?
Typical family style.
Yeah,
seeing
Mr. Lin and Ms. Ye,
and your parents,
they're a bit childish.
So I had to step up
and be the reliable one.
How do you plan to be mature?
I'll be
as gentle and reliable as you,
as organized as you,
as calm and composed as you,
like you...
Like me what?
Forget it.
What do you mean?
Why are you laughing?
How about being as rich as me?
I'm not rich at all.
My grandpa
paid for the new house.
You're moving?
Yeah.
We need a bigger place
for the extra person.
No wonder my mom said
your family asked her
for Zhou Yang's mom's
contact information a few days ago.
It seems to be for the renovation
of the new house.
Your family contacted my mom?
Yes.
But your mom couldn't take it.
She's been quite busy lately.
She works long hours every day.
Maybe she can't take it.
No.
She's working on a project
in Fanghe.
She can't take on work in Yibei.
Fanghe?
Yes.
You... You must know it.
Zhou Yang, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Your mom was transferred to Fanghe
to work on a project a month ago.
Didn't you know?
She doesn't come home every day, does she?
It takes an hour
to get to Yibei from Fanghe.
It must be exhausting to commute daily.
Here.
Yang.
The soup is ready.
Here.
Dinner is ready, Yang.
Come on.
Dig in.
Try the soup.
Mom,
are you going on a business trip?
No, I'm not.
I was just tidying up the room
and took the suitcases out.
I'll put them away later.
Have some soup.
Drink it while it's hot, Yangyang.
Are you very busy recently?
I see you go out
early every day.
Yes.
I'm busier
than before.
Actually,
if you are busy,
I can take care of myself.
Don't say that.
Isn't it my duty
to take care of you?
Alright, don't worry about it.
Just focus on your studies,
okay?
Here, Yangyang.
Thank you.
How's work going?
Any
new projects
you can tell me about?
Yes.
I've got several projects
that are quite challenging.
I'll show you the plans later.
Okay.
Are they all in Yibei?
Yes.
All in Yibei.
By the way,
there's an apartment
has a very special style.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Mom, eat.
Zhou Yang.
What's wrong with him?
Don't go over yet.
Let him be alone for a while.
What happened to him?
What do you think?
His mom...
Practicing on his own.
Still not good enough for him.
He's in a bad mood.
Give me the ball.
Give it to me.
Answer my question,
and I'll give it to you.
You can keep it.
I'm done playing.
I'm not here to play anyway.
Then what are you here for?
To annoy you?
I saw how you were just now,
couldn't even get the ball.
I know why
you're in a bad mood,
but bottling it up inside
and sulking
isn't helpful.
You might as well play a game with me
to vent your emotions.
Maybe you'll feel better.
I don't need it.
Thanks.
If your aunt knew
you were like this,
do you think she would feel better?
Actually,
I can understand
why she didn't tell me.
I just feel a bit sad.
Not for myself,
but
for her.
She works so hard.
So,
you should be happy every day.
Otherwise,
her efforts would be in vain.
Alright,
let's play a game.
Okay.
How's the game today?
Pretty good.
Fu Binyan,
why are you here?
I have something to tell you.
When did you get here?
Did you come as soon as school was over?
Or what?
Then why don't you go in?
I saw you two playing basketball,
so I didn't want to disturb you.
You should have told me.
If I had known you were coming,
I wouldn't have put in so much effort.
Now that the boss is here,
I'll just step aside.
I'm leaving now.
Take your time.
Bye.
Let's go.
We're running out of time.
Where are we going?
You'll know in a minute.
Why do we suddenly go to Fang He?
My mom
should have gone back by now.
We're not going to find your mom.
Then what?
I just want you
to take this route.
I know what you're worried about.
But this isn't something
that can be solved
with just a few words.
So instead of wasting words,
I thought I'd let you experience it for yourself.
Experience what?
The scenery your mom sees
every day as she commutes back and forth.
Seeing this,
I hope it will make you
feel a bit more at ease.
Thank you.
Fu Binyan,
have you ever thought
if your mom hadn't given birth to you,
would she have had
a better life than now?
I never thought about it.
Why?
She gave birth to me,
it was her own decision.
Every choice she made
was well considered.
Why do you ask?
Because I feel
I've been holding her back.
Come on, my boy.
Let's have a toast.
Come on.
Congratulations to mom
for taking on a new project independently.
Is this your first full project
back in the design circle?
That's right.
This is a milestone
for mom's return to the workplace.
From now on,
I'll keep working hard
and try to celebrate more with you,
okay?
Okay.
Come on,
let's eat.
It's getting cold.
Hello, ma'am,
this way, please.
Wen.
Yangyang,
long time no see.
Do you remember me?
I used to be an intern
your mom.
I even helped you
with your homework when you were little.
Long time no see.
What a coincidence.
Wen,
I heard you're working
at Geometric Design.
Their projects aren't huge,
so the competition is low.
It's a good fit for you.
I'm mainly focusing on
commercial space design.
I've just landed
a few projects recently.
I remember
you also wanted to
develop in this direction.
I'll take you to see it if you're free.
We'll see.
Congratulations!
You're doing great.
Thank you.
If it weren't for you,
retiring bravely back then,
going home to have a baby,
there wouldn't be room for us to rise.
You are my guide.
I always remember that.
Not at all.
This is all your own effort.
Yang,
try this.
It's really good.
Yang.
Dad,
pull over.
What's taking so long?
I've been chatting with Wen for a while.
Long time no see.
It's rare to meet up.
Sit down and eat together.
It's been a long time
since you've seen your son.
Waiter,
two more sets of cutlery.
No need to bother.
I have something to do later.
I won't disturb you.
Yang,
dad will come to see you another day.
We'll be going now.
Mom,
try this.
Thank you, son.
Mom,
I recommend a
particularly delicious milk tea.
You'll definitely like it.
Okay.
I want it with full sugar.
I'll order it for you right now.
If it weren't for me,
my mom
would be
just like that auntie,
doing what she loves
and shining bright,
instead of
spending hours on the bus every day
and still having to cook for me
and take care of me.
You're really overthinking it.
Coming and going,
that's Aunt Xiao's choice.
That phrase about giving up space
is just someone else's definition.
Just listen to it.
Aunt Xiao's decision
is not for others to define.
So do you think she
would regret it?
When you were quietly
watching the scenery
along the way,
how did you feel?
I was thinking
this is the route
my mom takes every day.
It feels very familiar.
Looking at those
streetlights,
tree shadows,
and houses,
it feels warm inside.
That's right.
Aunt Xiao is willing
to spend two hours commuting every day.
She's not regretting it,
but because she knows
Zhou Yang is waiting for her.
Besides,
who says she's not shining anymore?
She secured
Fang He's project all by herself.
Her light has always been there.
What you need to do
is to
shine your light
on her one day.
Got it?
Fu Binyan,
are we almost there?
After getting off,
we'll head back home right away.